

QIANQIAN.W Senior UI/UX Designer

STATEMENT

I am a designer with very refined taste and absolute care for detail. I am curious to learn about the users and have empathy on their pain points. And I take great pride in my ability to think outside the box, and my attention to details has always generated successful results of an improved user experience.

EXPERIENCES

10/2019 - Present

Senior UI/UX Designer

@ Leadvisor

Work closely with the executive team, define the product vision that sets the direction and guides the product development team based on the product exist Create low-fidelity wireframes for the internal communications, design dynamic and interactive prototype, and turn the team's ideas into testable artifacts

03/2018 - 09/2019

Product Designer

@ Jyve

Collaborated with product managers and engineers to solve design problems and create flexible and scalable UI and UX solutions for mobile apps Interviewed the target user, built the user flows for the core product platforms Developed low-fidelity designs, wireframes, as well as highly functional and interactive prototypes, and created the necessary assets and graphic elements

05/2017 - 03/2018

Product Designer

@ Pillow

Worked with Engineer and Product team to design interaction and user interface for the dashboard and responsive websites following a systematic process Performed as a leading designer for marketing launch including ad banners, brochures, door hangers, email campaigns, powerpoint presentations, iconography, and landing pages

05/2016 - 01/2017

Web Designer & Developer

@ VolunteerMatch

Worked with Client Service & Support team to strategize and build new help center website through sitemaps, wireframes

Developed Help Center websites in Zendesk utilizing HTML CSS Javascript and template language

10/2015 - 12/2015

UI/UX Designer

@ KidzJet

Developed pixel-perfect wireframe and mock-ups for KidzJet web-based dashboard and mobile application for both passenger and driver Participated in all phases of the product development lifecycle from ideation and definition to interface design, user research, and testing

06/2015 - 10/2015

UI/UX Designer

@ Hubtag Inc.

Designed and refreshed mockups for Hubtag live streaming software dashboard, and enhanced users experience by providing new responsive website layout

SKILLS

Sketch HTML User Research Adobe Photoshop CSS Interactive Design Adobe Illustrator Sass **Animation Creation** Adobe Premiere Javascript Speed Wireframing Adobe After Effect jQuery Concept Development Adobe Indesign Front-end Development Wordpress

EDUCATION

09/2016 - 05/2019

Academy of Art University

Master of Art in Web Design & New Media

(206) 953 0326 qianqiandesign@gmail.com

qqwangdesign.com

09/2013 - 06/2015

University of Washington, Information School

Master of Science in Library and Information Science

08/2009 - 06/2013

Shanghai University, Department of Library and Archives

Bachelor of Arts in Library and Archives